What feedback are they getting? Which two stocks are being
discussed? Good afternoon, tell me.
I actually came a little late because
I was thinking that if 20,000 is hit then we will
celebrate, but that 10 point is
probably what they are doing. Never less. Dealers are
obviously in celebration mode, but there is an
effort note from their side. Nifty has
gone above C80, so there are some
positions in the market, but specifically
talking about the stock, there is an
8% increase in ICC Lombard open interest and then they are
buying here. If you
look at the dealers, they feel that they can take a BTST trade here
for targets ranging from 1420 to 1430. Apart from this, Vedanta is a
STBT or position short trade, they are
suggesting it to their clients from both sides
and even today they feel that the stock should be sealed here. The
stock is weak,
those who feel that the levels are between 270 to 272 and today it
opened on the short side.  The interest is about two
percent bigger, so this is extra, which
they find weak, okay, when did you bring the shift once?